snapretail.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | SnapRetail

Last Updated: March 9, 2017

This is the Privacy Policy for the SnapRetail website (www.snapretail.com) and any and all other sites owned, operated and/or managed by SnapRetail, LLC, a Delaware limited liability company (referred to as “SnapRetail”). SnapRetail values your trust and understands that you may be concerned about how your personal information may be used and shared. We are committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you and about you (a “User”) and how we use that information.

If information is provided about you from any organization that has some relationship or partnership with SnapRetail, including but not limited to content sharing, technology integration, lead generation or reselling, that organization shall be referred to herein as an “Affiliate.”

This statement describes our privacy practices and how we collect and use information. By visiting www.snapretail.com or any other website operated and managed by SnapRetail (collectively, the “Site”), you are accepting the practices described in this notice.  

## Important Information

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify or amend this policy at any time. If we ever change our privacy policy in a material fashion, we will post any changes on this page and/or send you an email so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Unless we state otherwise, the changes to our privacy policy will affect only the information we collect after the effective date of the change. If you continue to use the Site after notification of a change, such use shall constitute your acceptance of the modified terms.

### Site Terms and Conditions of Use

If you visit this Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this privacy policy and the applicable Terms and Conditions for User, including, without limitations, its provisions relating to limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and governing law. If you are concerned about our privacy practices, please contact us, and we will work to resolve your concerns.

### Comments & Feedback

We welcome your feedback. If you have questions or comments about our privacy practices, feel free to send us an email at privacy@SnapRetail.com or write us:

SnapRetail, LLC  
Attn: Privacy  
100 South Commons, Suite 102  
Pittsburgh, PA 15212

### Correct/Update

This site provides users the following options for changing and modifying Personal Information previously provided:

  * You can send us an email to privacy@SnapRetail.com
  * You can send a letter to the mailing address above

Please include your name and your SnapRetail username in any such correspondence.  

## Information We Collect

### Personal Information You Provide About Yourself

We receive and collect information that you submit on this Site or provide us in any other way (“Your Personal Information”). We use Your Personal Information to provide Users with a more personalized experience, to respond to User requests, to communicate with Users, to provide products and services to Users, to administer sweepstakes and contests, to enhance the operation of the Site, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze Site use, to improve our product and service offers, and to tailor User experience with third parties as provided in this Privacy Policy. For example, if you send our customer service an e-mail, we may use your comments and feedback to tell others about our services, and may post your comment in our marketing materials or on our Site. In the case that your comments may contain personal information such as your name, we will obtain consent from you to post your name along with your comment prior to posting your comment for public view. In addition, if you use our Site to send information or a product to another person, we may store your personal information. We may also use Personal Information to troubleshoot, resolve disputes, accomplish administrative tasks, contact you, enforce our agreements with you, including any applicable Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities.

### Personal Information You Provide About Others

Some of the services on our Site may require you to submit on this Site or provide in any other way the personal information of third parties (the “Personal Information of Others”) in order for those services to properly function. These third parties may include, without limitation, friends, consumers, retailers, vendors, etc. For example, if you are a Subscriber, you will need to input the Personal Information of Others into Site Services such as the Email Marketing Service in order to utilize some of the Service’s functions. This Privacy Policy also governs any such Personal Information of Others you submit on this Site or provide in any other way. If you submit on this Site or provide in any other way the Personal Information of Others, you represent and warrant that you have the appropriate permission or rights to provide to us or submit such information and such use is permitted in any privacy policy which governed your original collection of the information.

### Automatic Information

We automatically receive and store certain information whenever you visit this Site. For example, like many web sites, we use “cookies” (described below) and obtain certain information whenever your Web browser accesses this Site. This information includes the internet protocol (IP) address of your computer, your browser software and operating system, your web server, the date and time you access our site, session information (such as download errors and page response times), information about your viewing, search and purchase history and information about the referring URL and the URL clickstream to, through, and from this Site. We use this information to monitor the usage and performance of this Site, to enhance your experiences and to determine aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.

### Information From Other Sources

We may receive information about you from other sources and add it to your account information. We may receive information from SnapRetail Affiliates and add it to your account.

### Information About Children

SnapRetail does not market or provide products or provide services to children. This Site is for adult use only. If you are under 18 years of age, you may not use this Site.

### Security Of Your Personal Information

We protect your information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the transmission of such information that you submit via the Site. For example, when a Service is purchased, the transmission of all sensitive information (billing address and credit card information) is encrypted by the SSL software. While we use reasonable steps to protect your information, given the continual evolution of threats, viruses and malware, we cannot guarantee that there will never be a security breach on our Site.  

## Navigational Information

### Personal Information You Provide about Yourself

To personalize and enhance your experience, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a cookie. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your computer’s hard drive. The help tab on the toolbar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting cookies, how to make the browser tell you when it receives a new cookie, or how to disable all cookies. You may visit our website without allowing the kinds of cookies described in this privacy policy to be set, however you may not have access to the full functionality of the website without some or all of these cookies.

### Third-Party Advertisers and Links

This Site may contain third-party advertising and links to and from other websites operated and maintained by separate companies. We do not provide your personally identifiable information to these third-party advertisers or Web sites. We have no responsibility for linked sites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. We encourage you to be aware when you leave this Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this Site.  

## How We Share Information We Collect

We protect all of Your Personal Information against unauthorized access or release in accordance with reasonable practices. We share Your Personal Information with third parties as follows:

  * **Affiliated Businesses:** We may share information with other businesses, such as SnapRetail Affiliates from whom, or with whose assistance, you purchase products or otherwise interact. This allows them to better serve you.
  * **Third-Party Service Providers:** We engage other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as order fulfillment, credit card payment processing, delivery services, postal mail and email, marketing assistance, and Consumer service. We may provide such service providers with access to personal information as needed to perform these functions.
  * **Offers and Promotions:** We may send offers to you and/or selected groups on behalf of an Affiliate.
  * **Market Research:** We may aggregate website visitor information for market research purposes. For example, we may use this information to evaluate the most popular email templates provided by the SnapRetail Service. We may share the results of this analysis with our Affiliates; however, your personally identifiable information will not be revealed, other than as described in this policy.
  * **Business Transfers:** As our business develops, we may buy or sell business divisions or subsidiaries. In connection with any such transaction, typically, Consumer information is one of the transferred assets, however, it remains subject to any pre-existing Privacy Notice. In the event that all, or substantially all of, SnapRetail’s assets are acquired, Subscriber and Consumer information will be one of the acquired assets.
  * **Compliance with Laws:** We may release personal information when we believe such release is appropriate to comply with applicable laws, rules or regulations, enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of SnapRetail, our affiliated businesses, or others. This may include, for example, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set forth above, you will receive notice when your personal information may be provided to third parties, and you will have the opportunity not to share the information.

## When We Use the Personal Information of Others

The Personal Information of Others you submit on this Site or you provide in any other way will belong to SnapRetail if any of the following conditions are met:

  * **Prior Information:**   If the Personal Information of Others you submit on this Site or you provide in any other way already exists in a SnapRetail database or in SnapRetail’s records in whole or in part.
  * **Affirmative Action:  ** If any action is taken by the owner of such information in contacting SnapRetail directly or doing business in any manner with SnapRetail, including without limitation, if some or all of the Personal Information of Others provided by you is used by its owner to register an account on a SnapRetail website; or some or all of such information is used by its owner in a connection with a purchase through a SnapRetail website or using SnapRetail’s technology or services.
  * **Purchase:  ** If the Personal Information of Others you submit on this Site or you provide in any other way already exists in whole or in part in a list or database of the Personal Information of Others purchased by SnapRetail from a third party vendor of such information.

If the Personal Information of Others you submit on this Site or you provide in any other way belongs to (is owned by) SnapRetail upon meeting any of the above conditions, SnapRetail may use such information without further notice to you, or permission from you, in any manner consistent with SnapRetail’s policies and practices.  

## Opting Out and Unsubscribing

### Electronic Communications

We regularly send emails, newsletters and other electronic communications to our Affiliates, subscribers and other users. If you do not wish to receive emails, newsletters, or other electronic communications from us, you may opt out of receiving these communications, except that any formal notice and/or communication set forth in the Terms and Conditions shall not be subject to the Opt-Out, unless or until you terminate your participation in any and all SnapRetail Services. Please see Choice/Opt-Out below.

### Choice/Opt-Out

You may unsubscribe from our marketing communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of our emails or by sending an email to service@snapretail.com.

### Removal

The site provides users the following options for terminating their account to remove their Personal Information from our database:

  * You can send us an email to privacy@SnapRetail.com
  * You can send a letter to the mailing address above

Please include your name and your SnapRetail username in any such correspondence.
